Samuel Zakaria

Medan Kota, North Sumatra, Indonesia



samuelzakaria28@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/samuel-zakaria

Summary

I am Samuel Zakaria, I am an active student of Information System at Pelita Harapan University, Medan Campus. I have UI/UX Designer experience, and as a full stack developer during college. That experience gave me basic insight into front-end and back-end, and I realized I had an interest in that area.

In my experience the skills I got I can use the language:

- 1.HTML
- 2. Php
- 3. CSS
- 4. Java

can also do:

- 1. Research users need information
- 2. Display development
- 3. Doing Documentation

Experience



UNY National IT Competition (UNITY) #10" Tahun 2022

Yogyakarta State University

Jan 2022 - Jun 2022 (6 months)

Unity is a national student competition in the field of technology by Yogyakarta State University. I was entrusted as the team leader, as well as the editor of my team.

Team Leader

- Responsible for ensuring that each member does their job description.
- Responsible for the ideas that will be collected in the competition
- Take full responsibility for the team, to provide good collaborative work.

Video Editors

- Responsible for making video concepts, shooting schedules, and checking video scripts.
- Responsible in the process of shooting video, and record audio.
- Responsible for the process of editing video competitions with high quality and good quality.
- Responsible for the process of uploading videos to the YouTube platform.

Team Leader

Spiritual Growth for Student UPH

Oct 2022 - Jan 2023 (4 months)

Become a team leader of the "Christmas Celebration 2022" work program.

Jobdesc:

- 1. Ensuring the Work Program runs well
- 2. Handling external relations with sponsors, speakers, supervisory groups, and superior groups
- 3. Handling internal relations with 80 team members
- 4. Ensuring each timeline is on target

Graphic Designer

Spiritual Growth for Student UPH Jul 2022 - Jun 2023 (1 year) Hold control over the organization's Publications

Education

Universitas Pelita Harapan

Bachelor's degree, Computer and Information Systems Security/Information Assurance 2021 - 2024

Licenses & Certifications

Memahami Konsep UI dan UX - Udemy UC-fd74c9c9-0e0e-4655-a78e-69b3bae9994e

Skills

Documentation • Team Leadership • Graphic Design • Research Skills • UI/UX • HTML • PHP • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)